(Leonard:)You're right, it is simple.
- Hey, Sheldon.
SHELDON: Penny.
(Penny:)Third floor tonight. Mixing it up?
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Penny:)I still don't understand
why you don't just go to dinner.
All right, let's say I go to dinner alone...
(Sheldon:)...and during the meal
I have to use the restroom.
(Sheldon:)How do I know
someone's not touching my food?
Good night, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Penny, hold on.
(Sheldon:)You sure things can't work out
with you and Leonard?
(Penny:)Excuse me?
(Sheldon:)I'm just wondering
if you really gave it the old college try.
(Sheldon:)Or in your case,
the old community-college try.
(Penny:)Okay, where is this coming from?
(Sheldon:)Leonard is upstairs right now
with my archenemy.
- Your archenemy?
- Yes, the Dr. Doom to my Mr. Fantastic.